Guide to the Walter Thabit papers, 1950-2004
Thabit, Walter papers, 1950-2004
- Series III. Planning Projects
  - Morningside Heights (MO)
    - MO-7: Morningside- SROs, 1964-1980 (Box 22, Folder 28)
      Single Room Occupancy. (Major issue on the institutional expansion effort)
    - MO-8: Morningside- Notes, Minutes, Flyers I, 1964-1980 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - MO-9: Monringside- Minutes, Etc., 1968-1971 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - MO-10: Morningside-MRC & General, 1964-1980 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - MO-11: MRC Meetings, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - MO-12: Morningside- Notes, Minutes, Flyers II, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - MO-13: Morningside Minutes, Flyers, III, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - MO-14: Morningside Renewal Council, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - MO-15: Calendars- Statements, 1964-1980 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      City Planning Commission and Board of Estimate calendars on Morningside items and MRC statements on them.
    - MO-16: Morningside Tenants Federation, 1964-1980 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      Includes Columbia University Students involvement
    - MO-17: Morningside- Institutional Expansion Background, 1964-1980 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - MO-18: Columbia Expansion, 1964-1980 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - MO-19: Progress & Promise of Columbia University C.U. Doc., 1964-1980 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      Columbia report and newsletters
    - MO-20: Piers Area- Manhattanville, Knickerbocker, 1964-1980 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      Waterfront area north of 125th Street Columbia University was keeping an eye on.
    - MO-21: Columbia University Various, 1964-1980 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - MO-22: Columbia Exp., 1964-1980 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - MO-23: Columbia Expansion Pei Meeting, 1964-1980 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      M.M. Pei's plan for Columbia expansion
    - MO-24: Rosen Corr, 1964-1980 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      Report on a consultant to the redevelopment authority giving Columbia all it wanted.
    - MO-25: Columbia- Community West 115th Street, 1964-1980 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      Resolution of conflict over these sites.
    - MO-26: Morningside House, 1964-1980 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      Expansion of a nursing home
    - MO-27: Hospital Expansion- St. Lukes, Knicerbocker, Morningside House, 1964-1980 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - MO-28: Jewish Theological, 1964-1980 (Box 23, Folder 16)
      Another Institutional expansion.
    - MO-29: Teachers College Building Program, 1964-1980 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - MO-30: Morningside - Early Acquisition, 1964-1980 (Box 23, Folder 18)
      Monitoring progress on first phase renewal sites
    - MO-31: Morningside - Shadrack Woods, 1964-1980 (Box 23, Folder 19)
      Architectural suggestions for the Douglas Circle Café
    - MO-32: Women's Hospital Site, 1964-1980 (Box 23, Folder 20)
      Another site that got developed
    - MO-33: Cathedral Parkway A.V., 1964-1980 (Box 23, Folder 21)
      Assessed valuation date for the project area
    - MO-34: Morningside - Area I, 1964-1980 (Box 23, Folder 22)
      Covers a number of early acquisition site issues
    - MO-35: Morningside Current 2nd Round, 1964-1980 (Box 23, Folder 23)
      Work on the second phase of renewal
    - MO-36: Notes on Second Round Acquisition, 1964-1980 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - MO-37: Cathedral Parkway Report, 1964-1980 (Box 23, Folder 25)
      Materials relating to the early acquisition progress report
    - MO-38: Morningside - Third Round, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - MO-39: Morningside Miscellaneous, 1964-1980 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - MO-40: Morningside - Miscellaneous Survey, 1964-1980 (Box 23, Folder 28)
      Survey of a strip of buildings to check rehabilitation potential.
    - MO-41: Morningside - Housing, 1964-1980 (Box 23, Folder 29)
      Various housing surveys and other items.
    - MO-42: Morningside - MABA Buildings, 1964-1980 (Box 23, Folder 30)
      Rehabilitation proposal
    - MO-43: West 114th St. Project, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      This project was out of the area but inspired a good deal of interest as a demonstration of what was possible
    - MO-44: Structural Data - Morningside, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      Structural data and analysis of rehabilitation needs prepared by H.D.A. consultant
    - MO-45: Morningside Population 1950-1970, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - MO-46: Morningside - Community Survey, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      A survey of community leaders
    - MO-47: 1973-1974 School Building Program & 1976-1977 projections, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - MO-48: Morningside - Schools, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - MO-49: Site 9- P 165 Polshek, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      Architect's proposed school renewal plan
    - MO-50: Area I- Feasibility Study- Site #9, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      Feasibility of a joint school/ residential development.
    - MO-51: Need for English as a Second Language, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - MO-52: Community School Board #3, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      Actions and meetings
    - MO-53: Cathedral Parkway- Manhattan Valley Schools, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - MO-54: High Schools, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - MO-55: Draft School Reports, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 13)
      Early reports to be included in final reoprt
    - MO-56: Daycare - Nurseries- Man Valley, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - MO-57: Notes on Proposal to Incorporate Health Satellite in the Douglas Circle Project, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - MO-58: Morningside - Health Areas- Birth Registration, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - MO-59: Morningside - Health Areas- Birth Registration, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - MO-60: Parks, Recreation, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - MO-61: Miscellaneous Community Facilities, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - MO-62: Morningside - Community Facilities, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - MO-63: Manhattan Valley Contract, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - MO-64: Background- Area 4, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - MO-65: Area IV- Programming, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 23)
      Mostly Area IV Committee reports.
    - MO-66: Manhattan Valley- Area IV, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 24)
      Various Documents and Analyses
    - MO-67: Manhattan Valley Preservation Report, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 25)
      Historic preservation application for designation
    - MO-68: Morningside - Area IV Meetings, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - MO-69: Manhattan Valley- 1970 Census Data, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - MO-70: Morningside - St. Joseph's Nursing Homes, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 28)
      One of the complex sites being planned.
    - MO-71: Apt. Dist. For Manhattan Day School Site, 3-Mar-70 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - MO-72: Manhattan Valley- Site Desc's, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 30)
      Descriptions of potential renewal sites
    - MO-73: Morningside - Building Bio. Files, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - MO-74: Summary of Site Descriptions, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - MO-75: Other's Surveys- Cath Parkway- Manhattan Valley, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - MO-76: Manhattan Valley- Survey Samples, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - MO-77: Manhattan Valley Comm. Gps., 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - MO-78: Morningside - Nursing Homes, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 36)
      A special analysis of potential for renewal
    - MO-79: Area IV- Early Action Planning, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 37)
      Selecting sites for a first phase.
    - MO-80: Map- Proposed Community Facility Morningside, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - MO-81: Manhattan Valley- Relocation, 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - MO-82: Manhattan Valley Housing Activity: Municipal Loans, Etc., 1964-1980 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - MO-83: MV- Project Rehabilitation, 1964-1980 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      A federal program
    - MO-84: Draft Part II Report Manhattan Valley, Dec-69 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - MO-85: Morningside Reports, 1964-1980 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - MO-86: Morningside Report, 1964-1980 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - MO-87: Morningside: Data Collection & Analysis, 1964-1980 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - MO-88: Morningside Renewal Progress, 1964-1980 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - The Columbia Student Revolts (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - West Side ORA - Replanning (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - West Side Urban Renewal Area (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Columbia Expansion (Box 69, Folder 29)
    - Morningside - Teachers College Plan (Box 69, Folder 30)
    - Institutional Expansion (Box 69, Folder 31)
    - Jewish Theo. Exp., June 1972 (Box 69, Folder 32)
    - Morningside Renewal Council (Box 69, Folder 33)
    - Morningside - Schools (Box 69, Folder 34)
    - Morningside - Early Acquisition (Box 69, Folder 35)
    - Manhattan Valley (Box 69, Folder 36)
    - Morningside Planning (Box 69, Folder 37)
  - Community Board (CB)
    - CB-1: Community Board #6- Minutes, Etc., 1973-1975 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      Minutes of the Planning and Zoning Committee which oversaw downzone study.
    - CB-2: Community Board #6 Commercial Use Survey, 1973-1975 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      Extensive survey of commercial uses in study area.
    - CB-3: Planning Board #6 Subway and Bus, 1973-1975 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      Analysis of impacts
    - CB-4: Community Board #6- Policy Issues Miscellaneous, 1973-1975 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - CB-5: Community Board #6 UNDC, 1973-1975 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      Rezoning for United Nations Development
    - CB-6: Community Board 6 Zoning Analysis, 1973-1975 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - CB-7: Community Board #6, 1973-1975 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      Zoning Variances
    - CB-8: Planning Board #6 Report Background, 1973-1975 (Box 25, Folder 14)
      Various items and draft reports
    - CB-9: Community Board #6 Interim Report, 1973-1975 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - CB-10: Community Board Final Report Draft, 1973-1975 (Box 25, Folder 16)
      Copies of drafts and final reports
    - CB6 Planning (Box 69, Folder 38)
    - CB6 Zoning Variances (Box 69, Folder 39)
    - CB6 Zoning Issues (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Methodist Hospital (MH)
    - MH-1: Methodist Hospital Background, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - MH-2: Methodist Hospital - Programming, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - MH-3: Methodist Hospital, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 19)
      Basic analyses and studies
    - MH-4: Methodist Hospital- Report Background, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - MH-5: Methodist Hospital Final Report, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - MH-6: Methodist Hospital Conference, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 22)
      Aftermath (of report)
    - Methodist Hospital - Planning (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Methodist Hospital - Plans/Data (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Methodist - Community Activity (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Cooper Square (CS)
    - CS-1: Health (Box 32, Folder 3)
      Variety of articles and other materials
    - CS-2: Cooper Square Health (Box 32, Folder 4)
      More materials including Cooper Square Committee directory of health services in the area
    - CS-3: Health Directories (Box 32, Folder 5)
      A number of health resources and directories
    - CS-4: Cooper Square Institutional Interview Background (Box 32, Folder 6)
      The actual interviews of local health providers
    - CS-5: Cooper Square Health Questionnaire (Box 32, Folder 7)
      Information on residential health survey
    - CS-6: Health Services in Cooper Square (Box 32, Folder 8)
      Committee's report on health services in the Cooper Square area.
    - CS-7: Cooper Square Health Demonstration Project (Box 32, Folder 9)
      Material dealing with a proposed demonstration health program
    - CS-8: Health Demonstration Application (Box 32, Folder 10)
      And related material
    - CS-9: Cooper Square Health Related Facility (Box 32, Folder 11)
      Controversy over a proposed supportive residential facility for the aged and mentally ill
    - CS-10: Cooper Square Homeless Men- Report Background (Box 32, Folder 12)
      Items dealing with conditions of homeless men.
    - CS-11: Homeless Men (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - CS-12: The Bowery Planning Problem (Box 32, Folder 14)
      Major report which resulted from and sparked a great deal of action on the Bowery
    - CS-13: Bowery Report- Form Ltr., December 24, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 15)
      Letters sent out with the Bowery Report
    - CS-14: Bowery- Homeless Men- Reports (Box 32, Folder 16)
      Reports of institutions and persons working with the Bowery population
    - CS-15: Bowery Men- Reports II (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - CS-16: Cooper Square Homeless Men Planning, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 18)
      Most of the files deal with the operations and actions of the Bowery Planning Task Force or similar organizations in their attempts to improve the lives of Bowery residents
    - CS-17: Camp LaGuardia (Box 32, Folder 19)
      Attempts to fund a plan to increase the capacity of this facility for the homeless
    - CS-18: Houston Hotel (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - CS-19: Potential Bowery Study Funding Sources (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - CS-20: Cooper Square Homeless Men, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      Meeting minutes and more.
    - CS-21: Cooper Square Bowery Men's Committee (Box 33, Folder 2)
      More minutes and activities of the committees.
    - CS-22: BPTF (Bowery Planning Task Force)- Background Notes on Services for Homeless Men (Box 33, Folder 3)
      Mostly reports and information
    - CS-23: Bowery Planning, 1974-1977 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      Minutes and activity
    - CS-24: R10 Zoning (Box 33, Folder 5)
      Articles, positions, calls to arms
    - CS-25: Cooper Square R 10 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - CS-26: Zoning Issue R 10 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - CS-27: R 10 Current (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - CS-28: Cooper Square Sponsorship, 1972-1974 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      Various items including draft letters of agreement between Cooper Square and developers
    - CS-29: C.C. Sponsorship - To 1971 end, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 10)
      Sponsorship negotiations with Methodist Church
    - CS-30: UDC (Urban Development Corp.) Agreements, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 11)
      Negotiations
    - CS-31: UDC (Urban Development Corp.), 1975 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - CS-32: Cooper Square- UDC (Urban Development Corp.) (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - CS-33: Cooper Square Glick Agreement, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 14)
      Ultimate Developer, negotiations
    - CS-34: Glick Agreement II (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - CS-35: Cooper Square Architects Screening Comm. (Box 33, Folder 16)
      The CS Committee selects an architect
    - CS-36: Sec. 8. 1975 Procedures, Etc. (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - CS-37: Cooper Square Concept Plan, July 1977 (Box 33, Folder 18)
      Early concept plan for the site, half of which was built upon.
    - CS-38: Cooper Square Sponsorship, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 19)
      Preliminary committee records, minutes and discussions on sponsorship issues
    - CS-39: Cooper Square Sponsorship, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - CS-40: Cooper Square Sponsorship, 1976-1977 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - CS-41: Cooper Square Sponsorship, 1977-1979 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - CS-42: Cooper Square Sponsorship, 1980-1983 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - CS-43: Community Development Committee (Box 34, Folder 5)
      Opposing the projected Moses clearance plan
    - CS-44: Cooper Square Income and Comp. w U.S. (Box 34, Folder 6)
      Analysis of Cooper Square incomes attacking the city's relocation report
    - CS-45: Housing Survey Analysis, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      Samples of original survey done for Alternate Plan
    - CS-46: Cooper Square- Technical Data (Box 34, Folder 8)
      Elements of the Alternate Plan for Cooper Square
    - CS-47: Cooper Square Alternate Plan (Box 34, Folder 9)
      First alternate plan for an Urban Renewal area.
    - CS-48: Alternate Plan Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - CS-49: Cooper Square Committee (Box 34, Folder 11)
      Part of battle to get City to commit itself to undertaking Alternate Plan without harmful changes
    - CS-50: Cooper Square Community activity (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - CS-51: Cooper Square- To 1965 I (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - CS-52: Cooper Square 9, 15, 17 East 1st Street Vacate (Box 34, Folder 14)
      Vacate order issued by Department of Buildings. Cooper Square Committee's first involvement with relocation
    - CS-53: Cooper Square Community Renewal/San Gennaro Fight (Box 34, Folder 15)
      Fight to save a site that was stolen for middle income housing
    - CS-54: Cooper Square Stationary (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - CS-55: Cooper Square Tax Exemption (Box 34, Folder 17)
      Tax exemption application and fund raising proposals
    - CS-56: Cooper Square Constitution & Contract (Box 34, Folder 18)
      Copy of an early constitution and negotiations for Cooper Square's first contract with the city
    - CS-57: Lower Manhattan Expressway Relocation Study (Box 34, Folder 19)
      Part of the fight against CS land being used for relocation
    - CS-58: Cooper Square Lower East Side (Box 34, Folder 20)
      Other Lower East Side issues
    - CS-59: Cooper Square- Lower East Side North (Box 34, Folder 21)
      Attempt to make Cooper Square subservient to an umbrella organization
    - CS-60: JPC (Joint Planning Council) Planning (Box 34, Folder 22)
      Organization of 30 housing groups on the LES fighting for low income housing
    - CS-61: Detailed Rehab. Costs (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - CS-62: Cooper Square Rehab. Costs Summaries (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - CS-63: CS Rehab Costing (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - CS-64: Cooper Square Rehabilitation- E (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - CS-65: Cooper Square Mortgage Info (Box 35, Folder 3)
      Mortgage info on Cooper Square properties
    - CS-66: Cooper Square Rehab. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - CS-67: Housing Survey Analysis (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - CS-68: Cooper Square- 5th to 6th St. Survey (Box 35, Folder 6)
      A detailed analysis of selected buildings on this block.
    - CS-69: Examples- Housing Preference Survey (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - CS-70: Examples of Filled Out Survey Forms (Box 35, Folder 8)
      Residential, structural and industrial.
    - CS-71: Cooper Square- Survey Forms (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - CS-72: SRO (Single Resident Occupancy) Survey- Manhattan Valley (Box 35, Folder 10)
      Borrowed from Morningside files to help.
    - CS-73: Cooper Square- Forms, Info on South of Stanton (Box 35, Folder 11)
      Non residential
    - CS-74: Cooper Square Non residential Interviews (Box 35, Folder 12)
      Shops, firms, theaters and other businesses.
    - CS-75: Cooper Square Non-Residential Interviews (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - CS-76: Cooper Square Planning Surveys/Land Use Issues, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - CS-77: Cooper Square Artists Housing (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - CS-78: Cooper Square- Artists (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - CS-79: AIR/Artist Committee (Box 35, Folder 17)
      Artist in Residence
    - CS-80: Artists Housing (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - CS-81: Cooper Square Schools- Board of Education (Box 35, Folder 19)
      Materials coming out of Board of Education
    - CS-82: Cooper Square Schools (Box 35, Folder 20)
      Analysis of CS needs
    - CS-83: Cooper Implementation Schools (Box 35, Folder 21)
      Struggle to get Board of Ed to agree on a K-2 school in Cooper Square
    - CS-84: Cooper Square- Cooper Union (Box 35, Folder 22)
      Struggle to direct Cooper Union expansion away from residential
    - CS-85: Cooper Square V (Box 35, Folder 23)
      Numbered files assembled for a projected writing project
    - CS-86: Cooper Square Material IV (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - CS-87: Cooper Square- Separation Fight (Box 35, Folder 25)
      Fight to keep renewal boundaries from expanding unduly
    - CS-88: Traffic & Street Closings (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - CS-89: Cooper Square Wyoming Building (Box 35, Folder 27)
      First building used for relocating Cooper Square artists
    - CS-90: Cooper Square- Public Housing (Box 35, Folder 28)
      Proposed project for Cooper Square
    - CS-91: Cooper Square Downtown Community School (Box 35, Folder 29)
      Neighborhood community facility seeking space in Cooper Square renewal area.
    - CS-92: Cooper Square Progress (Box 35, Folder 30)
      Indicates that little progress has been made on implementation. Written two years after the Early Action Plan was adopted by the cities.
    - CS-93: Cooper Square- Early Action Activity (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - CS-94: Cooper Square Early Action Planning II (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - CS-95: Cooper Square Publications (Box 36, Folder 2)
      Reports and long letters to officials
    - CS-96: Cooper Square Church of All Nations (Box 36, Folder 3)
      Major Community facility
    - CS-97: Cooper Square Early Action Report (Box 36, Folder 4)
      Related materials
    - CS-98: Channel1, ABC Stage City (Box 36, Folder 5)
      Commercial Buildings where commercials are made.
    - CS-99: Cooper Square VI (Box 36, Folder 6)
      Correspondence
    - CS-100: Cooper Sq. Miscellaneous (Box 36, Folder 7)
      Material from Cooper Square files
    - CS-101: Cooper Square Report (Box 36, Folder 8)
      Related to Early Action Plan report
    - CS-102: Cooper Square Early Action- Plan Approval (Box 36, Folder 9)
      Attempts for Planning Commission approval
    - CS-103: Cooper Square Early Action Plan- Approval II (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - CS-104: Cooper Square Early Action Planning II (Box 36, Folder 11)
      Planning scheduling and procedural materials
    - CS-105: Cooper Square Programming II (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - CS-106: C.S. Operations Planning, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - CS-107: Cooper Square Report, October 1972 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - CS-108: Cooper Square Implementation, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - CS-109: Cooper Sq Relocation (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - CS-110: Cooper Square Relocation (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - CS-111: Cooper Square Implementation Planning (Box 36, Folder 18)
      Working on actions needed to implement of the Early Action Plan.
    - CS-112: Cooper Square Implementation (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - CS-113: Cooper Sq. Replanning, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 20)
      A new planning effort, replacing the 25 year old Alternate Plan approach
    - CS-114: Cooper Square- Project Arts Comm. (Box 36, Folder 21)
      The $100,000 art works in Thelma Burdick Houses, the first Cooper Square new construction
    - CS-115: Thelma Burdick Hss. Implementation (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - CS-116: Cooper Square JASA Fight (Box 36, Folder 23)
      The second Cooper Square new construction project, and the fight to integrate it.
    - CS-117: Cooper Square, Pre-1970 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - CS-118: Cooper Square, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - CS-119: Cooper Square Minutes, Flyers, Statements II, 1970-1971 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - CS-120: Cooper Square Minutes, Flyers, Statements II, 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - CS-121: Cooper Square, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - CS-122: Cooper Square, 1975-1976 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - CS-123: Cooper Square, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - CS-124: Cooper Square, 1978-1979 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - CS-125: Cooper Square, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - CS-126: Cooper Square, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - CS-127: Cooper Square, 1980-1981 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - CS-128: Cooper Square, 1982-1983 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - CS-129: Cooper Square, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - CS-130: Cooper Square, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - CS-131: Cooper Square, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - CS-132: Cooper Square, 1987-1988 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - CS-133: Cube Building/Cooper Square, 1986-1987 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - CS-134: Cooper Square, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - CS-135: Cooper Square, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Cooper Square Chronology (Box 64, Folder 30)
    - Planning Papers to Cornell (Box 64, Folder 31)
    - Housing/Planning, 2003 and after (Box 64, Folder 32)